americanis.net 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - AIS

AIS is revising its privacy statement as we finalize changes to our new Website. Please watch this page for an updated privacy statement in coming weeks.

This privacy statement was last updated on 8/08/08. AIS has created this privacy statement in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Website, www.americanis.net.

**What is a Privacy Policy?**  
AIS created a privacy policy (described herein) to show our dedication and commitment to the privacy of the users of our website. Please read the following to gain an understanding of our privacy policy. If you have any questions regarding this policy, contact AIS and a AIS representative will respond to your query as soon as possible.

**What information do we collect from users and how is it used?**  
AIS is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy. At AIS we do not collect any personal information, unless you choose to share such information. If you do choose to share personal information via some form of correspondence, such information will not be shared, sold, or rented to others whatsoever.

**Correspondence**  
If you correspond with us via e-mail, we may gather the information in a file specific to you. We only collect the information that you provide to us. We will not sell, share, or rent the information that you share with us to others. Like many other websites, AIS collects information about users” utilization and navigation of our site. This information helps us to design our site to better suit our users” needs.

**Does the AIS website use cookies? If so, how are cookies used on the website?**  
Cookies are small files placed on your computer that contain only a unique number. We use this number to recognize your computer when a user of your computer returns. Like most major websites, AIS uses cookies on certain pages of our site. These cookies strictly identify your computer, our cookies do not contain any personal information about you.

**What are the policies of linked sites and other third parties?**  
This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Although you may interact with hosting companies as a result of visiting our site, or link to other sites or third parties via our website, AIS is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or the content of linked sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy whenever interacting with any website.

**How will I know about changes in the Privacy Policy?**  
AIS reserves the right to update this privacy policy from date and time to time. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes. However, we will only use Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the Privacy Policy that was in effect at the date and time the information was collected. If at any point we should decide to use that information differently, we will notify users by way of e-mail so that users can approve or disapprove of such use.

Contact Us Now to learn more about AIS.
